影院公映字幕 @字幕库2891968287
Mm-mmm.
You're alive.
What are you dreaming,little angel?
Well...
Try again.
Well, that's the bestI can do for now.
I'm really grateful, Doc.
I'll be getting some overtimenext week.
Yeah, pay me when you can.
Here,I got these for you.
My wife works outat Farm 22.
Thank you.
See you next time.
Keep getting paid in fruit
and we'll be pickingthese ourselves.
Hello, sleepyhead.
Hi.
How do you feel?
Okay.
Any pain anywhere?
No.
- Numbness?- No.
Motor dysfunction?
I'm a little hungry.
Eat this.
Get your sugar levels up.
Taste receptors are working.
Thank you.
You'll like this a whole lotbetter with the peel off.
I don't mean to be rude...
but am I supposedto know you?
Actually...
we haven't met.
I'm Dr. Dyson Ido.This is Nurse Gerhad.
And do you know who I am?
Well, we were hoping...
you'd fill in that part.
Since you'rea total replacement cyborg...
and most of your cyber bodywas destroyed...
we can't find any records.
But your very human brain was miraculously intact.
Theoretically, you should remember something.
Oh. Well...
It's still pretty blank.
No, it's completely blank,actually.
I don't even know my own name.
Let's look at the bright side.
Your tears are working.
Mmm.
That's so good.
What do you call this?
Yeow! What's that?
- Zalem.- Oh!
The last ofthe great sky cities.
- What holds it up? Magic?- No.
Something stronger.Engineering.
And down here,we have Iron City.
With all its charm.
Dr. Dyson Ido. That's you.
While I'm learning names,do you have one for me?
Alita.
It's a nice name.
I love it.
Can I keep it?
At least until I can remember my real name?
- Mm-hmm.- Thank you.
Okay.
- Do you want to take a look?- Yes.
Why are there so many languages?
Um, after the big war I told you about...
The Fall.
After The Fall,only Zalem was left...
and survivors came here from all over the world.
Everybody down here works for Zalem.
The Factory, the Farms...
Does anyone ever go up to Zalem?
We should go.
Nobody from down here ever goes up.
It's a rule that's never broken.
What?
Oh!And he takes him down hard!
What is that?
It's Motor ball.
That's so cool.
Nothing you need to be wasting your time watching.
Alita.
One minute, please.
Hi.
Hello.
You want some?
Here you go.
Can I hug you?
Hi.
Step aside.
Out of the way.
Outstanding.
Why don't you watch where you're going?
I gotta admit...
I never saw anybody challenge a Centurion before.
Whoa. You're heavy.
I mean...
Oh.
You're a cyborg.
Sorry, I was just admiring your hand.
Can I see?
Wow.
It's really nice work.
Did Doc Ido do it?
He built all of me.
Except my core. That's mine.
Well, he did a really great job.
Hey, what are those things?
The Centurions?
What planet are you from?
Ido found me in the Scrapyard.
- The Scrapyard?- Mm-hmm.
But that would mean...
Hey, Doc.
I got those driver-boards you were looking for.
Alita is new here.
She's still learning about things.
I gotta go.
I'll drop those off later.
I need a rebuild on a quad servo.
Maybe I'll see you around.
Who is that?
Hugo.
He's a hard worker, but...
Alita, come on,let's go home.
- Hugo.- Let's go home.
There's the damn Jackers
that ripped me to shreds standing right there.
And that vale madre Centurionwouldn't lift a finger.
Why would anyone wanna take your arms and legs?
Torque coupling.
Those Jackers want your parts for the black market.
To supply the Motorball games.
You were lucky.
Another girl was murdered last night, right near there.
Yeah, I heard that guy carves girls up...
and sells their body parts.
Sorry, Doc.
For now, I don't want you out after dark.
Is that understood?
Okay.
And if you go out during the day
don't wander too far from this neighborhood.
Okay.
Promise?
I promise.
Hey, kid.
Hey, what's your problem?
Who's the girl?
My new assistant.
I was surprised to see her in our daughter's body.
You were supposed to have destroyed that years ago.
- I couldn't.- Clearly.
And did you tell her who you built that body for?
Our daughter is dead, Chiren.
- You need to let it go.- Oh.
It's obviously not me that's clinging to something here.
Over here!
- Hugo.- Hey, Alita.
Is this Motorball?
It's just a scrimmage.
Do you wanna join in?
Come on, every kid's gotta play Motorball.
Sure, why not?
I want usto be a team again.
I have a great new setup...
and equipment...
worthy of your skills.
Together, we can build the finest champions
this game has ever seen.
Could be my ticket home.
When are you going to realize there is no way back?
It just does not happen.
Vector can make it happen.
I can't believe you trust Vector.
He has very high connections.
I won't help you build monsters.
I'm going to get back to Zalem somehow.
I'll claw my way there with my bare hands if I have to.
Hey, everyone,this is Alita.
Hi.
Best way to learn is to go in.
Pass the ball!
That's it.
Lean into your turns,look for an opening.
I think I'm getting it!
You can let goof the remote now.
Oh, crap.
- Come on, get her!- Come on, get her!
Cut her off!
Koyomi, pass her the ball.
And she got it! She got it!
Get her!
Sorry, princess.
Nice, Tanji, thanks.
She's never played before.
Sorry.
Got this!
Mine!
You got me!
Good shot.
Your freak girl friend's got some serious malfunctions.
I'm really sorry.
She humiliated you so severely.
All right,I'll see you tonight.
And, uh,she's not my girlfriend.
Whatever.
You've got some talent for this game.
I've got to get home now.
Ido wants me in the house before dark.
Do you want a ride?
So you can't remember anything?
I'm trying to.
Family, friends,favorite food?
Nothing. Well, maybe oranges.
But that's just since yesterday.
- Oranges?- Uh-huh.
Nope. Unacceptable.
Here, check this out.
Thank you very much, Senora.
And here you go.
Thank you.
You ready?
Try this.
Trust me.
It's chocolate.
Mmm.
- That is so great.- It's good, right?
I have a favorite food now.
- Thank you.- This is my favorite food.
Well, I wouldn't call it that.
I would.
Hey, look. Check it out.
It's a Hunter-Warrior.
He's a bounty hunter. Named Zapan.
Scanning for his mark.
I wouldn't wanna be that guy.
Look at that sword.
All guns are out lawed in Iron City.
Punishable by death.
Anything that challenges Zalem.
Didn't I tell you to be homebe fore dark?
What's the big deal?I just lost track of time.
Yeah. Don't trust anyone.
People do terrible things to each other here.
What happened to your arm?
Here, eat this.
You okay?
You still need proper nourishment for your brain.
You have any chocolate?
It's a harsh world.
The strong prey on the weak down here.
You gotta stay focused on your dream.
What's your dream?
I'll show you.
This is my secret place.
Best view in town.
Wow.
Really cool.
No. Look.
That view.
Oh.
Right.
I wonder what it's like up there.
Better than this dump down here.
Listen.
It's stuff from the Factory going up to Zalem.
But the tubes are just for cargo, not for people.
If I was as strong as you
I'd climb that tube to Zalem right now.
They don't let anybody up there.
Yeah, that's what they want you to think.
You just gotta know the right people.
- I happen to be connected.- Oh.
You gotta be willing to do what it takes.
Whatever it takes.
Funny thing is,you've seen it.
You just can't remember.
What do you mean?
Doc found you in the Scrapyard.
All that stuff is dumped from Zalem.
So you must be from up there.
I guess so.
If you could just tell me what those eyes have seen.
I wish I could.
I keep trying to remember, but...
It's still a blank.
I'm starting to feel like I wasn't very important.
Just an insignificant girl
thrown out with the rest of the garbage.
- No! Stop!- Alita!
Don't do it!
Oh, no.
It's a trap.
Looking for me, Doctor?
Or should I say,Hunter-Warrior?
"Hunter-Warrior"?
Oh, no.
Looks like he's got us.
Don't move.
Hey, thanks for bringing a girl.
That's gonna save us some time.
Nice shot, for a Meat-Boy.
No!
You came to rescue me?
That is so sweet.
You have nice eyes.
He's mine.You can have the girl.
So long as I get his eyes.
Alita, run!
My God.
Rip that flea!
You are so beautiful.
I wanna rip you open and see if you're ugly inside.
Like the others.
Watch her die.
Come here, little flea...
so I can pinch your head off.
Hi-yah!
99!
On your left!
Hi-yah!
You'll pay, little flea.
Grewishka does not forget.
I'm coming for you.
Both.
Grewishka does not forget!
When I was fighting,I remembered something.
I was in a huge battle.
You surprised me.
Well,you surprised me, too.
Before The Fall...
there were police to stop criminals.
Now, the Factory pays us to do the dirty work.
Hunter-Warrior 17739.
You are a Hunter-Warrior.
You stay here.
Don't kill anyone.
Bounty for the cyborg Nyssiana was 20,000 credits.
You should've told me who you really are.
And do you do it for the money?
I take the money.
Otherwise the clinic would've closed long ago.
I do this work for other reasons
I'd rather not talk about.
You have to talk about it.
Something during the fight triggered a memory.
I was on the moon.
You know more about me than you're saying.
Whose body is this?
Who am I?
This was your daughter?
You built this body for her?
Her name was Alita.
She was really looking forward to waking up
with legs that could run.
You built her a pair of fast legs.
She never got to use them.
She was murdered.
What happened?
A patient of mine came to the clinic one night
looking for drugs.
I was a tuner for the Motorball games...
and I had made a machine body for him of obscene strength.
He was my demon,coming back to me.
Hey! What are you doing there?
Alita couldn't get out of the way fast enough.
Her mother, Chiren,
couldn't deal with Alita's death.
Maybe she just couldn't deal with me.
So I went hunting.
I needed to kill him.
Maybe I was just hoping that he would kill me.
It brought no peace.
There were other demons like him out there...
and I felt, somehow, I was responsible for all of them.
So I registered as a Hunter-Warrior.
There's nothing noble about it.
Did you ever find peace?
I found you.
I'm not your daughter.
I don't know what I am.
I do.
Have a look at your original Cyber-core.
This is your brain.
A normal healthy teenage girl's brain.
If there is such a thing.
But this is your heart.
Part of your original core...
powered by an Anti-Matter Micro-Reactor.
So I've got a strong heart?
You have a heart strong enough
to power all of Iron City for years.
This is lost technology.
Nobody's made this stuff since...
before The Fall.
Yeah, right.
So I'm 300 years old?
Sweetheart, you are.
I don't want my players losing unless I tell them to.
It can't be left to chance.
You promised me champions.
And you promised me the best of everything.
Get those military servos I asked for.
You don't have a winning attitude.
Just be ready for tomorrow's game.
Help me.
Grewishka?
Why should I waste my talent on you?
Look what she's done to me.
Ido's little cyber girl.
What did you say?
The woman in my memory called me 99.
What you saw was a flash of your previous life.
Who was I?
In time, you'll remember.
I wanna rip her in half.
Grewishka.
Oh, how the mighty have fallen.
Are we stripping him for parts?
I need you to look at something.
It's a Telepresence Chip.He's wired.
Somebody in Zalem is riding him.
There are watchers behind the eyes all over the city.
Pretty common now.
I'd just as soon remove it...
while I'm rebuilding him.
Why are you wasting time
on this burnt-out street junk?
It's a personal matter.
Do you like your job, Vector?
If you like your position
and the many comforts that come with it...
I strongly suggest you listen to Dr. Chiren.
Nova.
My apologies.
Who did this to Grewishka?
A little cyborg girl.
Though the impact points
are evidence of extraordinary power...
I don't understand how she could create
such force with such a small body.
It was not the power of the body that did this.
It was the mind.
She knows the fighting techniques of Panzer Kunst.
Rebuild Grewishka.
Have him bring her to me.
Dead.
He's gone.
Not gone.
Repatched.
You're a clever woman, Doctor.
And determined to reach your goal at any cost.
So I'll make you this offer.
If and when you have pleased me...
I will grant you the destiny you seek.
Zalem.
You'll send me to Zalem?
I'm there right now.
Consider my services engaged.
There is no bounty on Grewishka.
But you reported it to the Factory.
Him killing all of those women...
Somebody's protecting him.
Who has the power to do that?
Someone far beyond us here.
We better stay off the street for now.
I wanna be a Hunter-Warrior like you.
Alita, that's impossible.
We could be a team.
Alita, this is dangerous,dirty work.
- I know.- No, you don't.
How is that your choice to make?
It's out of the question.
I might need a life-or-death situation
to remember who I was.
Even if it's just for a second.
Alita, some things are better left forgotten.
I don't want blood on these hands, too.
Then I'll find out for myself.
Alita.
I'm just tired of it.
He just wants me to be his perfect little girl.
So, you gonna live by his rules or yours?
What a battle!
These two have been going at each other all match.
Welcome to Motorball.
Jashugan has got the ball.
Claymore attacks!
Jashugan takes him out!
Masakus sends Jashugan flying!
Kutty now with the ball,one point.
Zariki is in hot pursuit.
- Wipe out, Zariki!- Whoo!
And he throws Kutty like a rag doll!
Come on.Let me show you something.
I know all the pit crews and tuners.
I'll introduce you around.
Who's the top player?
Right now, I'd say Jashugan
has the best chance of making Final Champion.
Camber's still off in the left bogie.
I was oversteering in turn six.
What's Final Champion?
It's the best thing a Motorball player can win.
Every few years, they choose a player that can't be beaten...
and he gets to go to Zalem.
Hey, Hugo.
Slow is smooth,smooth is fast.
Do it once, do it right.
Juggernaut needs to pit,right now.
Do you like to lose?
Then get him in here.
Claymore is a rebuild.Why is he not tracking?
Alita's here.
That's Vector.
He basically runs Motorball.
We do a lot of business with his team.
Selling parts to him and his new tuner.
Chiren.
Let's go, guys. Come on,get me back out there.
What? You're not the only one with connections.
Kutty closing inon Juggernaut.
Kinuba has Kutty in his sights.
Oh! Kinuba went through him
like laundry with those Grindcutters.
Is that weapon even legal?
Kinuba's too strong with that new weapon.
He's screwing up the odds.
You know...
I could really use his Grindcutters...
for our other project.
Crimson Wind making her way through the field.
So, what do you think?
I like it.
Yo, Hugo. We gotta go.
Hey, something's come up.
- Where are you going?- I just gotta do something.
Can you get back okay?
Yeah, sure.
Can you go out tomorrow?
I wanna show you this place me and Tanji know.
It's out in the Badlands.
It might help with your memory.
I'd appreciate that.
Thanks.
For everything.
Wow!He is throwing down!
Whoo!
Oh, shit!
- What the hell?- Shit.
Hurry up!
You're dead!
You little runts!
I'm gonna smash your skulls!
You can't do this to me!
- Ready.- Give me.
Careful.
You street punks!
I'm gonna make you pay for this.
Nice work.
Compliments to your crew.
Thank you, sir.
I'll pass it on.
Hey, man, where's my cut?
Hey, when you gonna tell your hard body
you jack cyborgs, huh?
I'm not.
And neither are you.
You afraid she's gonna cut you loose?
Get the Grindcutters over to Chiren right away.
Use the service gate.
Go.
Vector, you prick.
I should've known.
What you should've known,my friend...
is that no one...
is greater than the game.
What's outside the city?
Not much.
The war wiped out all utilities
and most everything else.
All we know is the sky cities fell all in one night...
when the enemy launched the last attack
with every ship they had.
Who was the enemy?
The URM.
United Republics of Mars.The U-R-M.
URM.
On that last night of the war...
the earth shook and the sky burned.
But in the morning,Zalem still stood.
It's just up ahead.
This ship is from the battle of Zalem.
I figured that maybe seeing stuff
from the war would help trigger your...
Salvagers have jacked some stuff
over the years for metal...
but it's all URM technology
so it's mostly been left alone.
- This is an URM ship?- Uh-huh.
You know, it's pretty hard to sell this stuff
since no one knows what it is...
Shh!
We have to goto the command deck.
It's forward.
How does she know that?
Hey, we can't get there.It's underwater.
How long do you think she can hold her breath?
I don't know.
Oh, this can't be good.
Forget it.
I won't do it.
But...
But you have to.
This would help us fight Grewishka
and anyone else he sends after us.
This body...
it has the power I need.
I feel a connection to it I can't explain.
This could be who I am.
You've been given a chance to start over
with a clean slate.
How many of us get that?
Why did an enemy war ship...
respond to me?
Because I knew that ship.
I've been on others like it,haven't I?
Haven't I?
Ouf, whatever you were,it's not who you are now.
No!
I'm a warrior, aren't I?
And you know.
You've always known.
This is called a Berserker.
It's a humanoid weapon-system created by the URM Technology.
Your core
was designed to interface with this type of body.
Your identity code activated it.
The instinctive fighting technique you use...
is Panzer Kunst,a lost combat art for machine bodies.
It was used by the Berserkers.
This is why you're drawn to conflict without hesitation.
It's part of your training.
You are not justa warrior, Alita.
You're an URM Berserker
the most advanced cyborg weapon ever created.
And that is exactly why
I will never unite you with this body.
That's fine.
Fine.
State your business.
I'm here to register as a Hunter-Warrior.
How'd it go?
You're a Hunter-Warrior,all right.
Doc's gonna be pissed.
Whose rules do I live by?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.Are you sure about this?
This place is just for bounty hunters, nobody else...
What do you think this is?
Besides, Ido says I'm drawn to conflict.
Oh. I remember you.
How's it going, little guy?
Good?
Just watch my back.
Oh, boy.
Hey, Zapan!Not the furniture.
What brings you in here, sweets?
Come to see the Hunters up close?
Not exactly.
Cup cake here is a bounty hunter.
What?
So, you went down
you filled out your application forms...
you got your ID badge...
and now you're just like us, yeah?
Let me introduce you
to some of your professional colleagues.
This is Master Clive Lee of the White Hot Palm.
He has over 200 confirmed kills.
207.
Well, and this is Screwhead
one of our most lethal bounty hunters.
And then, there's McTeague...
the Dogmaster,with his Hellhounds.
His biggest problem is having enough left to identify after
so he can collect the bounty.
And then, there's me.
Zapan.
Keeper of the legendary Damascus Blade.
Honed to a monomolecular edge.It slices armor like butter.
Forged before The Fall by the lost arts of URM metallurgy.
And who did you kill to acquire it?
A Hunter-Warrior is a solitary predator.
You'll be competing against us for the kill.
You can see what you're up against.
Thanks.
I came to ask for your help...
against our common enemy,Grewishka.
He's being protected by the system
and continuesto rampage unchecked.
And now,he's after Ido and me.
So I'm calling on you...
my Hunter-Warrior brothers.
Let's band together
and defeat him once and for all.
Any takers? Hmm?
No?
Big surprise.
You know, normally,I wouldn't take a rookie under my wing...
share my knowledge.
I'm willing to make an exception in your case...
if you'll cut loose Meat-Boy over here
and let me buy you a drink.
Hey, watch it.
And what could I learn from a loud mouth pretty boy...
who spends all of his money on his face?
Maybe I'll pully our arms and legs off
roll your head around in the street.
Maybe that'll teach you some manners.
You might mess up your hair.
You gonna take that, Zapan?
He's scared of the pretty girl.
Aah!
You do not deserve such a weapon.
I heard you were the heroes of Iron City.
I am not impressed.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm gonna need you to stand way back.
I will take on anyone in this room.
And if I win...
you fight alongside me.
This bitch broke my nose.
Yes, I did.
Heroes?
All I see are junkyard punks,assorted cyber-trash...
and a bunch of drunken Motorball burnouts
too slow to play the game.
Thanks, Hugo.
Oh, no.
Hold it!
Knock it off!
Or no more free repairs!
I'm with her.
Sorry about this.
You and I are going to have a little talk.
No, we had our talk.
You didn't leave me another choice.
Don't move.
It's Grewishka.
What's happened to him?
Well, to answer your question...
I've had a little upgrade.
I'm only here for the girl.
Ah, she's all yours.
What about the rest of you?
There ain't no bounty on this guy, Doc.
Not our problem.
It's all right, Ido.
Aw.
The only one with courage.
So innocent.
Iron City is no place for innocents, little flea.
I do not stand by in the presence of evil.
Come to my world.
Come, little flea.
Alita! No!
Welcome to the under world. My world.
From here, there are worlds above worlds above worlds...
going farther up than you can imagine.
And the trash of each one flows down to the one below...
'til it all ends up here.
It's where I used to live.
And it's where you're going to die.
Dance, little flea.
I was forgotten here to rot.
But I was saved...
remade...
by the same hand that shapes your destiny even now.
Whose hand?
My master, Nova.
What do you know about me?
You have the soul of a survivor.
You'll never give up.
Aah.
Know what is hidden.
Always ask...
what is it that you are not seeing?
Nova?
He is the dragon that must be slain.
Again.
Look at you.
Where are you going?
What's the matter?
My little toy doesn't want to play anymore?
I'll turn you into a living pendant
to adorn my chest.
Then I can hear your voice every moment of the day...
pleading for mercy!
Hi-yah!
Fuck your mercy.
No!
Break off!
He wasn't a dog lover.I hate that.
Oh, come on.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You think you can replace us that easily?
Bring her back as many times as you like.
No one will dare harm you again.
It's the adaptive technology of the Berserker body.
The shell is reconfiguring
to her subconscious imageof herself.
I've never seen anything like it.
It's making micro-adjustments throughout every system.
Looks like she's a little older than you thought.
Well, look at you.
Well, you were right.
A warrior's spirit needs a warrior's body.
It draws in air,generating an arc plasma...
but how you control it,I don't know.
Didn't exactly come with a manual, did you?
It's some kind of weapon.
Now you know who you are.
But that's just a shell.
It's not bad or good.
That part's up to you.
Check these out.
Pretty fresh, right?
Alita!
Wow.
You're...
- Back together?- Very back together.
You look...
different.
It's all Nano-tech.
It's a bunch of stuff even Ido hasn't figured out yet.
So are you stronger than you were?
Yeah. And faster, too.
It feels...
more me.
You know,some guys might be
intimidated by a girl like you.
Really? Why is that?
'Cause you could rip my arm off
and beat me with the wet end.
Well, then,don't piss me off.
Why don't you like her?
I just never got the whole hardbody thing.
And besides, she's URM.
It means she was probably the enemy at one point.
Yeah, 300 years ago.
Get over it.
I'm a lot more touch sensitive, too.
A lot higher density of force feedback and...
texture sensors.
You wanna try it?
You can feel this?
Yes.
Close your eyes.
How about this?
Yes.
Where am I now?
You're...
with me.
Does it bother you...
that I'm not completely human?
You are the most human person I have ever met.
He won't even let me fix his eye.
He says he wants the pain.
Enough.
Nova.
You have failed me.
Stand.
You will never triumph until you understand what she is.
She's the last of her kind.
The finest weapon of the URM Technarchy.
I need you to destroy this Alita.
I need you to bring me her heart.
I live only for her death.
I hate when he does that.
This is not a man who tolerates failure.
I'm not trusting my future to a piece of iron.
What do you have in mind?
To dreams.
I like your drive, Hugo.
You have a solid future with my team.
My future's in Zalem.
I remember your promise every day.
To send me up.
When I get you a million credits.
Personally...
I'd rather rule in hell than serve in heaven.
We'd be at the bottom of the food chain up there
but down here...
we can live like kings.
So...
Tell me about this friend of yours.
Alita?
Is that her name?
Alita. Hmm.
Hi.
What happened to you?
I wound up hanging out with Vector.
Some alcohol was involved.
Apparently.
So, Vector?
Is that your connection for getting into Zalem?
Yeah.
Oh.
I was hoping may be you'd wanna stay.
Hey, it's not right away.
I still gotta raise the rest of the money first.
It's okay.
It's your dream.
I know it's what you've always wanted.
You know...
I was always so sure.
Now you come along...
nothing's clear anymore.
How much more do you need before you can go?
90k.
90k?
I can make that in bounties.
I'll just figure out who has
the highest prices on their heads...
and then I'll take them out.
No, I can't ask you to do that for me.
I'd do whatever I had to for you.
I'd give you whatever I have.
What are you doing?
I'd give you my heart.
Take it.
It's got an URM Micro-Reactor for a power supply
probably worth millions.
With your connections,you can find a buyer...
you could make enough for both of us to go to Zalem...
and then we just find a cheap replacement...
No.
Come on, you buy and sell parts all day long.
Don't just do things for people.
No matter how good you think they are
or how deserving they are.
It's all or nothing with me.
This is who I am.
I know.
It's okay.
Put it back.
That was pretty intense, huh?
Yeah, that was very intense.
Sorry.
Maybe there's another way.
Vector wants you to try out for Second League.
What?
You become a big Motorball star
make a pile of money...
we can go to Zalem together.
What are you talking about?
I can't be a pro-Motorball player.
Ali...
you could be a champion.
You win this tryout...
every scout will be killing each other to get to you.
We'll be home free.
Only if you'll be my coach.
Well, if that's what it takes.
That's what it takes.
Are you going to kill her?
No.
Much worse.
Ido, can a human love a cyborg?
Why?
Does this cyborg love a human?
Mm-hmm.
A human can love a cyborg...
but you have to keep your mind on the game, Alita.
It can get very rough out there.
Even for a tryout.
Try these.
Did you make these for me?
Yes.
They won't make you any faster. It's regulation.
But at least they won't fail you.
Here's our deal.
You go in there, you race
you win,you come back right here.
You wear all of these pads,especially this one.
I don't need all this crap.
Yes, you do.
Remember...
if you wreck this body,I can't fix it.
- This is URM technology.- Yes, I know.
Now, go find a place to watch
because you're making me nervous.
Good luck.
Bye.
Thank you for coming on such short notice.
You are the scum of the game.
But tonight,you are hand-picked scum.
Because tonight is not a game.
It is a hunt.
I'm paying 500,000...
to the one who kills the girl called Alita.
Hey.
Where are you? The tryout's about to start.
I'm on my way.
There's something I've gotta do first.
I'm doing this for us,remember?
You can't miss it.
I won't. Trust me.
Please, just stop.
I didn't do anything to you.
It's just business.Nothing personal.
Tanji, stop!
Using my name?
Man, what's wrong with you?
I can't do this anymore.
What's the matter? You're already gone half the time.
Now you show up with this line of crap!
It's the little hard body,isn't it?
Listen, it's over.Do you understand?
I'm out.
And if you had any brains,you'd leave this behind, too.
For good.
You should've jacked that bitch when you had the chance.
Would've been on your way to Zalem right now.
Well, very professional.
Hey, man,we don't want any trouble.
If this is your mark,we're sorry. He's all yours.
Hugo.
Jacking cyborgs.
Your little girlfriend might take that
kind of personally,don't you think?
Hmm?
But you know girls.
She'll probably get all weepy and forgive you...
when I show her your head.
There's no marker out on me.
There will be.
Murder pulls a tight little bounty...
even with gutter trash like you.
I never killed anyone.
You just did.
She thinks she can punk me, huh?
Hugo, run!
Next up is Second League tryouts.
Will the Factory practice team report to the line?
The winner tonight will make it one step closer...
to qualifying for the Champions League.
Well, that is one tough lineup.
This is gonna be one heck of a match tonight.
That's no Factory team.
What?
These two punks in the back...
there are bounty markers on them.
And the other guys,they are Hunter-Warriors.
And here comes tonight's one new prospect.
Okay, then, folks,give it up for Alita!
Hugo brought her right to us.
- What'd you promise him?- Hmm.
I'm sending him to Zalem,of course.
Alita! Alita!
Hey.
Since there is only one new prospect...
- What's up?- ...there will be no teams.
The name of the gameis Cut-throat.
Go easy on me, guys.
Sure, kid.
No worries.
- Alita!- What are you doing?
It's a setup.You gotta get outta there.
They're gonna kill you!
Which ones?
All of them!
Players, 10-second warning.
Five seconds...
The new kid, Alita,
takes possession right off the snap.
A slow Tuesday night just got hotter than the playoffs.
Looks like the fans have themselves
an underdog darling...
with the face of an angel and a body built for battle.
Maybe a little Motorball
will break out in the middle of this fight.
Oh, crap.
Oh! Looks like it's
"No rules Tuesday" out there, folks.
Ouch!You know that hurts!
Stinger's got Alitain a lot of trouble.
She must've said somethingin the locker room
that these guys did not like.
Number 99...
Alita!
Ali, it's me.
I've got a big problem.
Hugo, this is not a good time.
He's trying to kill me.
Who's trying to kill you?
Zapan, the Hunter-Warrior.
He killed Tanji.
What do you mean?
Now, he's coming for me.
Not sure our Battle Angel
can get out of this one.
Oh, shit. Here he comes!
Where are you?
I'm headed to the old church.
Okay. I'm coming.
I can't believe it!Incredible!
I've never seen anything like this.
Hey, I'm almost there.
Got it.
Where are you going, huh?
Looks like your Hugo hasn't been entirely honest with you.
Is it true?
Ali...
you don't understand.
I never killed anyone.
We only jacked parts.
We paralyzed them and stripped them, that's all.
I needed the money for Zalem.
Step aside and let me do my job.
Touch him again and I will kill you.
Interference between
a licensed Hunter-Warriorand his kill...
is a violation of Factory Law and the Hunter's Code.
He's mine!
Then make the kill.
Come on, Hunter-Warrior.
Tonight, you becomeone of us.
Mm-mmm.
You know, there's no room for love or mercy
in the Hunter's Code.
Let me make it easier for you.
Hugo!
Deliver the criminal Hugo, Bounty 9107.
Wanted for the crime of murder.
You better finish him before we do!
It's Hunter Law!
I have to get you to Ido.
No. Centurions.
If you go back out there with me alive
they'll kill us both.
What did you do? What did you do?
I didn't kill that guy.
But what does it matter?
I tore people apart.
People like you, for money.
Where were you tonight?
I went to go stop the others.
- And tell them I quit.- Why?
Because I love you.
God, I'm sorry.
Did you find them?
No.
They're gone.
You're so cold.Please don't die.
Please don't.
I'd give him my life if I could.
Maybe you can.
You have violated Factory Law and the Hunter's Code
by protecting a wanted felon.
Where is the criminal Hugo, Bounty 9107?
Hugo is dead.
I claim the bounty.
Hunter-Warrior 26651.
Claim confirmed.
Ah.
Yeah, that's a cute trick.
You think this is gonna work, huh? Hmm?
Give me that.
Violation.
Hunter-Warrior Zapan...
stealing another's bounty
is against Factory Law and the Hunter's Code.
Thanks.
My face.
My... My face!
My face!
No!
How is he?
This city corrupts even good people.
He's good.
He's stable.
Chiren's surgical technique was brilliant.
There's no brain damage.
Vector was running a scam.
If you're born on the ground,you stay on the ground...
and no amount of money can change that.
The only one way to get from the lower world to Zalem...
is to become Final Champion.
You can't buy your way up there.
But how do you know that for sure?
I was born there.
I've removed it myself,the Mark of Zalem.
With our daughter's illness
Chiren and I were forced to descend here to Iron City.
And the man responsible for our exile...
the watcher behind the eyes...
is Nova.
You had her heart in your hands...
and you let her live.
- I did.- Why?
Because I'm a doctor.
And...
I'm a mother.
And somehow I forgot that.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm out.
Chiren, wait.
Don't you think it's time you went to Zalem?
I could send you up there right now.
What I want...
it isn't up there.
I have to do something.
I'll come back for you.
This is my fault.
Don't ever feel sorry for yourself.
You're the only one built for this.
Thank you, Father.
Vector!
Hostile intention detected.
Surrender your weapon.
Security report.
Violation! Violation!
Did you get her?
Security?
You were never going to send Hugo to Zalem, were you?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I always keep my promise to send people up.
Like Dr. Chiren here.
Nova demands body parts for his experiments.
Especially, the brains of people he admires.
And that is the only way anyone ever gets to Zalem.
It took you long enough.
I knew you wouldn't wait for your fate
to find you, little flea.
Get up.
Defense Ring!
Finish the mission.
Destroy Zalem.
I know who my enemy is.
And I know he's watching us now.
And you're just his slave.
And I'm just an insignificant girl.
Speak.
No. No. No. Wait.
Speak!
What do you want me to say? I will say anything.
Not you.
Him!
So we finally meet, Alita.
Not your real name, of course.
Nova?
Where are you?
Home. As we speak.
Feet up.
Well, my girl
you've certainly exceeded my expectations.
Killing my champion Grewishka.
Most impressive.
And turning a selfish creature like Chiren.
I didn't see that coming.
So, when you walk out of here,the Factory won't stop you.
This time.
I don't need your permission to live.
Others might.
Your Dr. Ido, for example.
And what about Hugo?
He's still alive, isn't he?
We will track him down.
Hmm.
I've found the only way to enjoy immortality...
is to watch others die.
You just lost a puppet.
Well, that looks fatal.
No matter.
Vector was getting tire-some.
You've made the biggest mistake of your life.
And what's that?
Underestimating who I am.
Then until next time.
Remember.
I see everything.
Alita.
Factory enforcers came looking for Hugo.
Somehow they knew he'd been kept alive.
I helped him escape,but they've sealed the city.
- They're going to find him.- Where is he?
He's trying to go up.
Hugo!
Hugo.
Stop.
You have to come down.We can't stay up here.
There's a bounty on me.This is the only way.
No, this is dangerous.We have to get down, now.
If I go back down there,I'm dead.
No. You have to listen to me, okay?
I've been right here before.
This is exactly where Nova wants you.
He's using you to get to me.
Come on,we have to go back down.
We belong up there, Alita.
We don't belong anywhere except together.
You'll always be running.
Together.
Come with me.
Please.
We could be free.
Okay.
No!
Hold on.
I got you.
Okay, okay. Don't move.
Don't move.
I'm gonna lift you up slowly.
Thank you...
for saving me.
I love you.
No!
It took her only a few months...
to rise through the ranks of the Second League.
And tonight,she makes her first appearance
in the Champions League.
Where she has a chance at becoming Final Champion...
and going to Zalem.
Alita! Alita! Alita!
Let's hear it for the Battle Angel herself...
number 99...
Alita!
Alita! Alita! Alita!
Subtitles by explosiveskull www.OpenSubtitles.org