Born of cold and winter air and mountain rain combining
This icy force both foul and fair
Has a frozen heart worth mining
So cut through the heart, cold and clear
Strike for love and strike for fear
See the beauty sharp and sheer
Split the ice apart
And break the frozen heart
Hup! Ho! Watch your step! Let it go
Beautiful! Powerful
Dangerous! Cold
Ice has a magic can't be controlled
Stronger than one, stronger than ten
Stronger than a hundred men
Born of cold and winter air and mountain rain combining
This icy force both foul and fair
Has a frozen heart worth mining
Cut through the heart, cold and clear
Strike for love and strike for fear
There's beauty and there's danger here
Split the ice apart
Beware the frozen heart
Come on, Sven!
Elsa. Psst!
Elsa!
Wake up. Wake up. Wake up.
Anna, go back to sleep.
I just can't. The sky's awake, so I'm awake
so we have to play.
Go play by yourself.
Do you want to build a snowman?
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Do the magic! Do the magic!
Ready?
This is amazing!
Watch this!
Hi, I'm Olaf and I like warm hugs.
I love you, Olaf.
--- - Hang on. - Catch me! - Gotcha!
-- - Again! - Wait!
Slow down!
Anna!
Anna?
Mama! Papa!
You're okay, Anna. I got you.
Elsa, what have you done? This is getting out of hand!
It was an accident. I'm sorry, Anna.
-- - She's ice cold. - I know where we have to go.
Ice?
Faster, Sven!
Sven!
Please... Help!
My daughter!
He is the King!
Trolls...?
Shush. I'm trying to listen.
Cuties. I'm gonna keep you.
Your Majesty!
Born with the powers or cursed?
Born. And they're getting stronger.
You are lucky it wasn't her heart.
The heart is not so easily changed
but the head can be persuaded.
Do what you must.
I recommend we remove all magic
even memories of magic to be safe...
But don't worry, I'll leave the fun.
She will be okay.
But she won't remember I have powers?
-- - It's for the best. - Listen to me, Elsa
your power will only grow.
There is beauty in it...
but also great danger.
You must learn to control it.
Fear will be your enemy.
No. We'll protect her. She can learn to control it. I'm sure.
Until then
we'll lock the gates. We'll reduce the staff.
We will limit her contact with people
and keep her powers hidden from everyone...
including Anna.
Elsa?
Do you want to build a snowman
Come on let's go and play
I never see you anymore. Come out the door
It's like you've gone away
We used to be best buddies
And now we're not. I wish you would tell me why
Do you want to build a snowman
It doesn't have to be a snowman
Go away, Anna.
Okay bye
The gloves will help. See...
-- - Conceal it. - Don't feel it.
Don't let it show.
Do you want to build a snowman
Or ride our bike around the hall
I think some company is overdue
I've started talking to the pictures on the walls
Hang in there, Joan.
It gets a little lonely all these empty rooms
Just watching the hours tick by
I'm scared. It's getting stronger.
Getting upset only makes it worse.
Calm down.
No. Don't touch me. Please. I don't want to hurt you.
See you in two weeks.
-- - Do you have to go? - You'll be fine, Elsa.
Elsa?
Please, I know you're in there
People are asking where you've been
They say have courage and I'm trying to
I'm right out here for you. Just let me in
We only have each other
It's just you and me
What are we gonna do
Do you want to build a snowman
-- - Welcome to Arendelle! - Merci, monsieur!
Watch your Steps please. The gates will opening Soon.
Why do I have to wear this?
Because the Queen has come of age.
It's Coronation Day!
That's not my fault.
-- - What do you want, Sven? - Give me a snack!
-- - What's the magic word? - Please!
A..A... a... a! Share!
I can't believe they're finally opening up the gates!
And for a whole day!
Faster, Persi!
Ah, Arendelle, our most mysterious trade partner.
Open those gates so I may unlock your secrets
and exploit your riches.
Did I just say that out loud?
Oh, me sore eyes can't wait to
see the Queen and the Princess.
I bet they're absolutely lovely.
I bet they are beautiful.
Princess Anna...?
Huh? Yeah?
-- - Sorry to wake you, ma'am but... - No, no, no. You didn't.
I've been up for hours.
Who is it?
It's still me, ma'am. The gates will open soon.
-- - Time to get ready. - Of course!
Ready for what?
Your sister's coronation, ma'am.
My sister's cor-neration...
It's coronation day!
The window is open! So's that door
I didn't know they did that anymore
Who knew we owned 8000 salad plates
For years I have roamed these empty halls
Why have a ballroom with no balls
Finally, they're opening up the gates
There'll be actual, real-life people
It'll be totally strange
But wow am I so ready for this change
'Cause for the first time in forever
There'll be music, there'll be light
For the first time in forever
I'll be dancing through the night
Don't know if I'm elated or gassy
But I'm somewhere in that zone
'Cause for the first time in forever
I won't be alone. I can't wait to meet everyone...
What if I meet "The one"?
Tonight, imagine me gown and all
Fetchingly draped against the wall
The picture of sophisticated Grace
I suddenly see him standing there
a beautiful stranger tall and fair
I wanna stuff some chocolate in my face
But then we laugh and talk all evening
Which is totally bizarre
Nothing like the life I've led so far
For the first time in forever
There'll be magic, there'll be fun
I could be noticed by someone
And I know it is totally crazy
To dream I'd find romance
But for the first time in forever
At least I've got a chance
Don't let them in. Don't let them see
Be the good girl You always have to be
Conceal. Don't feel.
Put on a show.
Make one wrong move and everyone will know
But it's only for today
It's only for today
It's agony to wait
Tell the guards to open up the gate
The gate
For the first time in forever
I'm getting what I'm dreaming of.
Be the good girl you always have to be.
A chance to change my only world.
Conceal.
A chance to find true love
Conceal. Don't feel, Don't let them know
I know it all ends tomorrow
So it has to be today
'Cause for the first time in forever
For the first time in forever
Nothing's in my way
I'm so sorry. Are you hurt?
Hey!
-- - I-ya, no. No. I'm okay. - Are you sure?
Yeah, I just wasn't looking where I was going.
-- - But I'm great, actually. - Oh, thank goodness.
Prince Hans of the Southern Isles.
-- - Princess Anna of Arendelle. - Princess...?
My Lady.
Hi... again.
Oh boy.
Ha. This is awkward. Not you're awkward
but just because we're...I'm awkward.
You're gorgeous. Wait, what?
I'd like to formally apologize for
hitting the Princess of Arendelle with my horse...
and for every moment after.
No. No-no. It's fine. I'm not THAT Princess.
I mean, if you'd hit my sister Elsa, that would be...
'cuz, you know...
Hello.
But, lucky you, it's-it's just me.
Just you?
The bells. The coronation.
I... I...
I better go. I have to...I better go.
Bye!
Your Majesty, The gloves.
Sem hon heldr inum helgum eignum ok
krýnd í þessum helga stað ek té fram fyrir yðr
Queen Elsa of Arendelle.
Princess Anna of Arendelle!
Here? Are you sure? I do not think I suppose to...Okay.
Hi.
Hi me...? Oh. Um. Hi.
-- - You look beautiful... -Thank you.
You look beautifuller. I mean, not fuller.
You don't look fuller, but more beautiful.
Thank you.
So, this is what a party looks like?
It's warmer than I thought.
And what is that amazing smell?
Chocolate.
Your Majesty. The Duke of Weaseltown.
Weselton. The Duke of Weselton..
Your Majesty
as your closest partner in trade
it seems only fitting that I offer you
your first dance as Queen.
Thank you. Only I don't dance.
But my sister does.
-- - Lucky you...- Oh, I don't think...
If you swoon, let me know, I'll catch you.
Sorry.
Like an agile peacock...
Speaking of, so great to have the gates open.
Why did they shut them in the first place?
Do you know the reason? Hmm?
No. No...
Oh, all right. Hang on.
"" They don't call me "The little dipper" for nothing.
Like a chicken...with the face of a monkey... I fly.
Let me know when you're ready for another round, My Lady.
Well, he was sprightly.
Especially for a man in heels.
-- - Are you okay? - I've never been better.
This is so nice.
I wish it could be like this all the time.
Me too...
But it can't.
-- - Why not? If... - It just can't.
Excuse me for a minute.
-- - Glad I caught you. - Hans!
I often had the whole parlor to myself to slide... Oops. Sorry.
Your physique helps, I'm sure too.
-- - What's this? - I was born with it
Although I dreamt I was kissed by a troll.
I like it.
Yeah, The whole thing! You got it.
Okay wait, wait. So you have how many brothers?
Twelve older brothers.
Three of them pretended I was invisible...
literally... for two years.
-- - That's horrible. - It's what brothers do.
And sisters.
Elsa and I were really close when we were little.
But then, one day she just shut me out, and...
And I never knew why.
I would never shut you out.
Okay, can I just say something crazy?
I love crazy.
All my life has been a series of doors in my face
And then suddenly I bump into you
I was thinking the same thing, because like
I've been searching my whole life to find my own place
And maybe it's the party talking
Or the chocolate fondue
But with you
I found my place
I see your face
And it's nothing like I've ever known before
Love is an open... door
Love is an open... door...door
With you! With you
Love is an open door
-- - I mean it's crazy. - What?
-- - We finish each other's... - Sandwiches!
That's what I was gonna say
I've never met someone who thinks so much like me
Jinx... jinx again.
Our mental synchronization can have but one explanation
You and I were just meant to be
Say goodbye
To the pain of the past
We don't have to feel it anymore
Love is an open... door
Love is an open door
Life can be so much more...with you... with you
Love is an open... door
Can I say something crazy...?
Will you marry me?
Can I just say something even crazier?
Yes.
Oops! Pardon. Sorry. Can we just get around you there?
Thank you. Oh, there she is.
Elsa! I mean... Queen...
Me again. May I present
Prince Hans of the Southern Isles.
Your Majesty.
We would like...your blessing...
of... our marriage!
-- - Marriage...? - Yes!
I'm sorry, I'm confused.
Well, We haven't worked out all the details ourselves.
We'll need a few days to plan the ceremony.
Of course we'll have soup
... roast, and ice cream and then...
Wait. Would we live here?
-- - Here? - Absolutely!
Anna...
12 Oh, we can invite all twelve of your brothers to stay with us...
What? No, no, no, no, no.
... Of course we have the room. I don't know. Some of them must...
Wait. Slow down.
No one's brothers are staying here.
No one is getting married.
Wait, what?
May I talk to you, please. Alone.
No. Whatever you have to say, you...
you can say to both of us.
Fine. You can't marry a man you just met.
You Can if it's true love.
Anna, what do you know about true love?
More than you. All you know is how to shut people out.
You asked for my blessing, but my answer is no.
Now, excuse me.
... Your Majesty, if I may ease your...
No, you may not. And I-I think you should go.
The party is over. Close the gates.
Yes, Your Majesty.
What? Elsa, no. No, wait!
Give me my glove!
Elsa, please. Please. I can't live like this anymore.
Then leave.
What did I ever do to you?!
Enough, Anna.
No. Why? Why do you shut me out?!
Why do you shut the world out?!
What are you so afraid of?!
I said, enough!
Sorcery. I knew there was
something dubious going on here.
Elsa...?
There she is.
Your Majesty! Long live the Queen! Queen Elsa...
Come drink with us.
Queen Elsa.
Your Majesty? Are you all right?
There she is! Stop her!
Please, just stay away from me.
Stay away!
Monster... Monster!
Elsa!
Elsa...
Wait, Please!
Elsa, Stop!
-- - Anna! - No.
The Fjord.
Snow?
Yes, snow!
-- - Are you all right? - No.
-- - Did you know? - No.
Look! It's snowing! It's snowing!
The Queen has cursed this land!
She must be stopped!
-- - You have to go after her...- Wait, no!
You! Is there sorcery in you, too?
Are you a monster, too?
No. No. I'm completely ordinary.
That's right she is.
In the best way.
And my sister's not a monster.
She nearly killed me.
-- - You slipped on ice... - Her ice!
It was an accident. She was scared.
She didn't mean it. She didn't mean any of this...
Tonight was my fault. I pushed her.
-- - So I'm the one that needs to go after her. - What?
-- - Yeah. - Bring me my horse, please.
Anna, no. It's too dangerous.
Elsa's not dangerous.
I'll bring her back, And I'll make this right.
-- - I'm coming with you...- No.
I need you here to take care of Arendelle.
On my honor.
I leave Prince Hans in charge!
Are you sure you can trust her?
I don't want you getting hurt.
She's my sister
She would never hurt me.
The snow glows white on the mountain tonight
Not a footprint to be seen
A kingdom of isolation
And it looks like I'm the Queen
The wind is howling like this swirling storm inside
Couldn't keep it in, Heaven knows I tried
Don't let them in, Don't let them see
Be the good girl you always have to be
Conceal, Don't feel, Don't let them know
Well, Now they know
Let it go. Let it go
Can't hold it back anymore
Turn away and slam the door
I don't care what they're going to say
Let the storm rage on
The cold never bothered me anyway
It's funny how some distance makes everything seem small
And the fears that once controlled me
Can't get to me at all
It's time to see what I can do
To test the limits and break through
No right, No wrong, No rules for me
I'm free!
Let it go! Let it go!
I am one with the wind and sky
You'll never see me cry
Here I stand and
Here I'll stay
Let the storm rage on
My power flurries through the air into the ground
My soul is spiraling in frozen fractals all around
And one thought crystallizes like an icy blast
I'm never going back
The past is in the past
Let it go! Let it go!
And I'll rise like the break of dawn
That perfect girl is gone
Here I stand in the light of day
Let the storm rage on!
The cold never bothered me anyway
Elsa! Elsa!
Elsa, It's me, Anna...
Your sister who didn't mean to make you freeze the summer.
I'm sorry. It's all my f-f-fault.
Of course, none of this would have happened
if she'd just told me her secret... ha...
She's a stinker.
Oh no. No. No. No. Come back. No.
Oooo-Kay.
Snow, it had to be snow
She couldn't have had tr-tr-tropical magic
... that covered the f-f-fjords in white sand and warm...
Fire!
Wandering Oaken's Trading Post.
And Sauna...
Big summer blow out.
Half off swimming suits, clogs
And a sun balm of my own invention, yah?
Oh, great.
For now, how about boots
Winter boots... and dresses?
That would be in our winter department.
Oh. Um, I was just wondering, has another young woman
The Queen perhaps, I don't know, passed through here?
Only one crazy enough to be out in this storm is you, dear.
You and this fellow... Hoo hoo.
Big summer blow out.
-- - Carrots. - Hah?
Behind you.
Oh, right. Excuse me.
A real howler in July, yes?
Where ever could it be coming from?
The North Mountain.
North Mountain.
40 That'll be forty.
4010 Forty? No, ten.
Oh dear, that's no good. See.
These are from our winter stock
where supply and demand have a big problem.
You want to talk about a supply and demand problem?
I sell ice for a living.
Ooh, that's a rough business to be in right now.
... I mean, that is really...
Ahem. That's unfortunate.
40 Still forty. But I will throw in a
visit to Oaken's sauna.
Hi, family.
10 Ten's all I got. Help me out.
Ten will get you this and no more.
Okay, just tell me one thing...
What was happening on the North Mountain?
Did it seem magical?
Yes! Now, back up
while I deal with this crook here.
What did you call me?
Okay. Okay, I'm-Ow! Whoa!
Bye bye.
No Sven, I didn't get your carrots.
But I did find us a place to sleep.
And it's free.
I'm sorry about this violence.
I will add a quart of lutefisk
so we'll have good feelings.
Just the outfit and boots, yah?
Reindeers are better than people
Sven, don't you think that's true
Yeah, people will beat you and curse you and cheat you
Every one of em's bad, except you
Oh, Thanks, buddy.
But people smell better than reindeers
Sven, don't you think I'm right
That's once again true, for all Except you
You got me, let's call it a night
Good night
Don't let the frostbite bite
Nice duet.
Oh, it's just you.
What do you want?
I want you to take me up the North Mountain.
I don't take people places.
Let me rephrase that...
Take me up the North Mountain...
Please.
Look, I know how to stop this winter.
We leave at dawn...
And you forgot the carrots for Sven.
Oops. Sorry. Sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't...
We leave now. Right now.
Hang on! We like to go fast!
I like fast!
Whoa, whoa! Get your feet down. This is fresh lacquer.
Seriously, were you raised in a barn?
Ew. No, I was raised in a castle.
So tell me, what made the Queen go all ice-crazy?
Oh well, it was all my fault.
I got engaged but then she freaked out because...
I'd only just met him, you know, that day.
And she said she wouldn't bless the marriage...
Wait. You got engaged to someone you just met?
Yeah. Anyway, I got mad and so she got mad.
And then she tried to walk away
and I grabbed her glove...
Hang on. You mean to tell me.
You got engaged to someone you just met?!
Yes. Pay attention. But the thing is...
she wore the gloves all the time
So I just thought, maybe she has a thing about dirt.
Didn't your parents ever warn you about strangers?
Yes, they did...
But Hans is not a stranger.
Oh yeah? What's his last name?
...Of-the-Southern-Isles?
-- - What's his favorite food? - Sandwiches.
-- - Best friend's name? - Probably John.
-- - Eye color... - Dreamy.
-- - Foot size? - Foot size doesn't matter.
Have you had a meal with him yet?
What if you hate the way he eats?
What if you hate the way he picks his nose?
Picks his nose?
And eats it.
Excuse me, sir. He's a Prince.
All men do it.
Ew. Look it doesn't matter, it's true love.
Doesn't sound like true love.
Are you some sort of love expert?
No. But I have friends who are.
You have friends who are love experts?
-- - I'm not buying it... - Stop talking.
... No, no, no. I'd like to meet these...
No, I mean it.
Shhh.
Sven, go. Go!
-- - What are they? - Wolves.
Wolves?
-- - What do we do? - I've got this.
You just... don't fall off and don't get eaten.
-- - But I wanna help... - No.
Why not?
Because I don't trust your judgment.
Excuse me?!
Who marries a man she just met?
It's true love!
Christopher!
It's Kristoff!
Duck!
-- - You almost set me on fire! - But I didn't.
Get ready to jump, Sven!
You don't tell him what to do!
I do! Jump, Sven!
But I just paid it off.
Uh-oh. No, no, no.
Grab on!
Pull, Sven! Pull!
I'll replace your sled and everything in it.
And I understand if you don't want to help me anymore.
Of course I don't want to help her anymore.
In fact, this whole thing has ruined me
for helping anyone ever again.
-- - But she'll die on her own. - I can live with that.
But you won't get your new sled if she's dead.
You know sometimes I really don't like you.
Hold up. We're coming.
You are?!
I mean, sure. I'll let you tag along.
-- - Arendelle... - It's completely frozen.
But it'll be fine. Elsa will thaw it.
-- - Will she? - Yeah.
Now come on. This way to the North Mountain?
More like this way.
I never knew winter could be so beautiful.
Yeah... It really is beautiful, isn't it?
But it's so white.
You know, how about a little color?
I'm thinking like maybe some crimson, chartreuse...
How 'bout yellow...no, not yellow.
Yellow and snow? Brrrr... no go.
Am I right?
-- - Hi! - You're creepy.
-- - I don't want it! - Backatchya!
Please don't drop me. Come on, it's just a head.
No!
All right, we got off to a bad start.
Ew, ew, the body!
Wait, what am I looking at right now?
Why are you hanging off the earth like a bat?
...Al'right. Wait one second.
-- - Oooh! Thank you! - You're welcome.
Now I'm perfect.
Well, almost.
It was like my whole life got upside down.
... Oh! Too hard. I'm sorry! I was just...
-- - Woo! Head Rush! - Are you okay?
Are you kidding me? I am wonderful!
I've always wanted a nose.
So cute. It's like a little baby unicorn.
What? Hey! Whoa.
Oh, I love it even more! Hah...
All right, let's start this thing over.
Hi everyone. I'm Olaf. And I like warm hugs.
Olaf?
That's right, Olaf.
And you are?
Oh, um... I'm Anna.
And who's the funky-looking donkey over there?
That's Sven.
Uh-huh. And who's the reindeer?
Sven.
They're...oh, okay...Makes things easier for me.
Ha. Aw, look at him tryin' to kiss my nose.
I like you, too!
Olaf, did Elsa build you?
Yeah. Why?
-- - You know where she is? - Yeah. Why?
Do you think you could show us the way?
-- - Yeah. Why? - How does this work?
Stop it, Sven. Trying to focus here.
-- - Yeah, Why? - I'll tell you Why.
We need Elsa to bring back Summer.
Summer?
Oh, I don't know why but.
I've always loved the idea of summer
and sun, and all things hot.
Really?
I'm guessing you don't have much experience with heat.
Nope!
But sometimes I like to close my eyes
and imagine what it'd be like when summer does come.
Bees'll buzz, kids'll blow dandelion fuzz
And I'll be doing whatever snow does in summer
A drink in my hand, my snow up against the burning sand
Prob'ly getting gorgeously tanned in summer
I'll finally see a summer breeze
Blow away a winter storm
And find out what happens to
Solid water, when it gets warm
And I can't wait to see, what my buddies all think of me
Just imagine how much cooler I'll be in summer
The hot and the cold are both so intense
Put 'em together, it just makes sense
Winter's a good time to stay in and cuddle
But put me in summer and I'll be a
Happy snowman
When life gets rough I like to hold on to my dream
Of relaxing in the summer sun just letting off steam
Oh the sky will be blue
And you guys'll be there too
When I finally do what frozen things do in summer
-- - I'm gonna tell him. - Don't you dare.
In summer
So, Come on! Elsa's this way.
Let's go bring back summer!
I'm coming!
Somebody's got to tell him.
No. No. You've got the bark facing down.
The bark needs to be face-up.
Bark down is drier.
-- - Bark up... - Bark down.
Cloak. Does anyone need a cloak?
Arendelle is indebted to you, Your Highness.
The castle is open. There's soup
[] and hot glogg in the Great Hall.
Here. Pass these out.
Prince Hans, are we just
expected to sit here and freeze
while you give away all of Arendelle's tradable goods?
Princess Anna has given her orders and...
And that's another thing
has it dawned on you that your Princess
may be conspiring with a wicked sorceress...
to destroy us all?
Do not question the Princess. She left me in charge
and I will not hesitate to
protect Arendelle from treason.
Treason?!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa, boy. Easy. Easy.
Princess Anna's horse. What happened to her? Where is she?
Princess Anna is in trouble.
I need volunteers to go with me to find her!
I volunteer two men, my Lord!
Be prepared for anything
and should you encounter the Queen
you are to put an end to this winter.
Do you understand?
So how exactly are you planning to stop this weather?
Oh, I am gonna talk to my sister.
That's your plan? My ice business is
riding on you talking to your sister.
Yup.
So you're not at all afraid of her?
-- - Why would I be? - Yeah.
I bet Elsa's the nicest, gentlest
warmest person ever.
Oh, look at that.
I've been impaled.
What now?
It's too steep. I've only got one rope
and you don't know how to climb mountains.
Says who?
What are you doing?
I'm going to see my sister.
You're going to kill yourself. I wouldn't put my foot there.
-- - You're distracting me... - Or there.
How do you know Elsa even wants to see you?
I'm just blocking you out 'cause
I gotta concentrate here.
You know, most people who disappear
into the mountains want to be alone.
Nobody wants to be alone. Except maybe you.
I'm not alone... I have friends, remember?
You mean the love experts?
Yes, the love experts!
Please tell me I'm almost there.
Does the air seem a bit thin to you up here?
- - Hang on. - Hey, Sven?
Not sure if this is going to solve the problem, but I found
a staircase that leads exactly where you want it to go.
Ha ha. Thank goodness. Catch!
Thanks! That was like a crazy trust exercise.
Now that's ice. I might cry.
Go ahead. I won't judge.
All right, take it easy boy. Come here, I gotcha.
Okay. You stay right here, buddy.
Flawless.
Knock... just knock...
Why isn't she knocking?
Do you think she knows how to knock?
It opened. That's a first.
You should probably wait out here.
What?
Last time I introduced her to a guy, she froze everything.
But. But... oh come on, It's a palace made of ice.
-- - Ice is my life. - Bye, Sven.
You too, Olaf.
-- - Me? - Just give us a minute.
Okay.
One... two... three... four...
Elsa? It's me... Anna.
Anna?
Wow... Elsa, you look different...
It's a good different... and this place.
-- - Is amazing. - Thank you.
I never knew what I was capable of.
... I'm so sorry about what happened. If I'd known...
No, it's okay.
You don't have to apologize.
But you should probably go, please.
But I just got here.
You belong in Arendelle.
-- - So do you. - No, Anna. I belong here.
Alone.
Where I can be who I am
without hurting anybody.
--585960 - Actually, about that... - 58... 59... 60.
Wait. What is that?
Hi, I'm Olaf and I like warm hugs.
Olaf?
You built me. You remember that?
And you're alive?
Um... I think so?
He's just like the one we built as kids.
So we were so close.
We can be like that again.
Slow down.
Anna!
No, We can't.
-- - Goodbye, Anna. - Elsa, wait.
No, I'm just trying to protect you.
You don't have to protect me. I'm not afraid.
Please don't shut me out again.
Please don't slam the door.
You don't have to keep your distance anymore
'Cause for the first time in forever
I finally understand
For the first time in forever, we can fix this hand in hand
We can head down this mountain together
You don't have to live in fear
'Cause for the first time in forever
I will be right here
Anna, please go back home
Your life awaits.
Go enjoy the sun and open up the gates
-- - Yeah, but... - I know! You mean well
But leave me be.
Yes, I'm alone. But I'm alone and free.
Just stay away and you'll be safe from me
-- - Actually, we're not - What do you mean you're not
I get the feeling you don't know
What do I not know
Arendelle's in deep deep deep deep snow
What?
You kind of set off an eternal winter... everywhere.
Everywhere?
It's okay, you can just unfreeze it.
No, I can't.
-- - I don't know how. - Sure you can.
I know you can!
'Cause for the first time in forever
I'm such a fool! I can't be free
You don't have to be afraid
No escape from the storm inside of me
We can work this out together
I can't control the curse
We'll reverse the storm you've made
Anna, please, You'll only make it worse
Don't panic
There's so much fear
We'll make the sun shine bright
You're not safe here
We can face this thing together
I can't
Anna. Are you okay?
-- - I'm okay. I'm fine. - Who's this?
Wait, it doesn't matter. Just... you have to go.
No, I know we can figure this out together.
How? What power do you have to stop this winter?
To stop me?
Anna, I think we should go.
No. I'm not leaving without you, Elsa.
Yes, you are.
Stop. Put us down!
Go away!
Heads up!
Watch out for my butt!
It is not nice to throw people!
Wow, wow, wow feisty pants. Ok, relax.
Just calm down. Calm down.
All Right. I'm Okay.
Just let the snow man be.
-- - I'm calm. - Great.
Come on!
See. Now you made him mad!
I'll distract him.
You guys go.
No, no, not you guys.
This just got a whole lot harder.
What are you doing?
I got him!
It's a hundred foot drop.
It's two hundred.
-- - What's that for? - I'm digging a snow anchor.
Okay. What if we fall?
There's twenty feet of fresh powder down there.
It'll be like landing on a pillow...
hopefully.
Okay, Anna. On three.
-- - One... - Okay. You tell me when...
-- - Two... - I'm ready to go... I was born ready! Yes!
Calm down.
Tree!
... What the... Whoa! That happened.
Ah. Ah. Man, am I out of shape.
There we go. Hey, Anna! Sven!
Where'd ya guys go? We totally lost marshmallow back there!
Hey. We were just talking about you.
All good things, all good things.
No!
This is not making much of a difference! Is it?
Olaf!
-- - Hang in there, guys! - Go faster!
Wait, what?
Kristoff!
Don't come back!
We won't.
Hey, you were right. Just like a pillow.
Olaf!
I can't feel my legs!
Those are my legs.
Hey, do me a favor, grab my butt.
Oh, that feels better.
Hey, Sven! He found us.
Who's my cute little reindeer?
Don't talk to him like that.
Here.
-- - You okay? - Thank you.
Um... how's your head?
I mean, It's fine. Ah... I'm good.
Ha. I've got a thick skull.
I don't have a skull... or bones.
So...
-- - So now what? - Now what?
Now what?!
Oooh! What am I gonna do?
She threw me out. I can't go back to
Arendelle with the weather like this.
... And then there's your ice business...
Hey, hey, don't worry about my ice business.
-- - Worry about your hair. - What?
Just fell off a cliff. You should see your hair.
No, yours is turning white.
White? It's... what?
It's because she struck you, isn't it?
Does it look bad?
-- - No. - You hesitated.
No, I didn't. Anna, you need help. Okay? Come on.
-- - Okay! Where are we going? - To see my friends.
-- - The love experts? - Love experts?!
And don't worry, they'll be able to fix this.
How do you know?
Because I've seen them do it before.
I like to consider myself a love expert.
Get it together. Control it.
Don't feel. Don't feel.
Don't feel!
Look, Sven. The sky's awake.
-- - Are you cold? - A little.
Wait. Come here.
So, about my friends...
Well, I say friends, they're more like family.
Anyway, when I was a kid, it was just me and Sven
until you know, they took us in.
-- - They did? - Yeah.
I don't want to scare you, they can be
a little bit inappropriate.
And loud... very loud...
They're also stubborn at times, and a little
... overbearing. And heavy. Really, really heavy. Which you...
But you know, you're okay. They're fine. They mean well.
Kristoff, they sound wonderful.
Okay then.
Meet my family.
Hey, guys!
They're rocks.
He's crazy.
Hey, Wow... I pretty recognize you, What's so much weigh?
I'll distract them while you run.
Hi, Sven's family! It's nice to meet you!
Anna, because I love you, I insist you run.
I understand you're love experts!
Why aren't you running?
... Okay. Um... I'm gonna go...
No, no, no. Anna, wait!
Kristoff!
Kristoff's home!
Kristoff! Kristoff's home! It's been too long!
Wait? Kristoff?
Yeah... Oh, let me look at you!
Oh, take off your clothes, Kristoff, I wash them.
Ah! No. I'm gonna keep my clothes on. Look.
it's great to see you all.
-- - But where's Grand Pabbie? - He's napping.
But look, I grew a mushroom.
And I earned my fire crystal.
I passed a kidney stone.
Kristoff, pick me up.
You're getting big! Good for you.
Trolls? They're trolls.
He's brought a girl!
She's like a little cupcake.
What's going on?
I've learned to just roll with it.
Let me see.
Bright eyes. Working nose. Strong teeth.
Yes, yes, yes. She'll do nicely for our Kristoff.
Wait. Oh, no.
You've got the wrong idea.
That's not why I brought her here.
... Right. We're not. I'm not...
What's the issue, dear?
Why are you holding back from such a man?
Is it the clumpy way he walks
What?
Or the grumpy way he talks
No.
Or the pear-shaped, square-shaped
weirdness of his feet
Hey!
And though we know he washes well
he always ends up sorta smelly
But you'll never meet a fella who's as sensitive and sweet
... That's nice, but...
So he's a bit of a fixer upper
So he's got a few flaws
His peculiar brain, dear
His thing for the reindeer
That outside a few of nature's laws
This is not about me!
So he's a bit of a fixer upper
But this we're certain of
You can fix this fixer upper up
with a little bit of love
Can we just stop talking about this?!
We've got a real, actual problem here.
I'll say...so tell me dear.
Is it the way that he runs scared
Or that he's socially impaired
Or that he only likes to tinkle in the woods
I do not need to know that.
Are you holding back your fondness
Due to his unmanly blondeness
Or the way he covers up
that he's the honest goods
He's just a bit of a fixer upper
He's got a couple a' bugs
No, I don't.
His isolation is confirmation of
his desperation for healing hugs
So he's a bit of a fixer upper
But we know what to do
The way to fix up this fixer upper
is to fix him up with you
Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. Enough!
She's engaged to someone else. Okay?!
So she's a bit of a fixer upper
That's a minor thing
This quote engagement is a flex arrangement
And by the way, I don't see no ring
So she's a bit of a fixer upper
Her brain's a bit betwixt
Get the fiance out of the way
and the whole thing will be fixed
We aren't saying you can change him
'Cause people don't really change
We're only saying that love's a force
That's powerful and strange
People make bad choices
if they're mad or scared or stressed
But throw a little love their way
throw a little love their way
And you'll bring out their best
True love brings out the best
Everyone's a bit of a fixer upper
That's what it's all about
Father, sister, brother
We need each other
to raise us up and round us out
Everyone's a bit of a fixer upper
But when push comes to shove
The only fixer upper fixer that can fix a fixer upper is
True, True, True, True, Love
Love, Love, Love, True Love
True-e-e-e-e-e
Do you, Anna
... take Kristoff to be your trollfully wedded...
Wait, what?!
You're getting married.
Anna!
She's as cold as ice.
There's strange magic here!
Grand Pabbie!
Come, come. Bring her to me.
Anna, your life is in danger.
There is ice in your heart, put there by your sister.
If not removed
to solid ice will you freeze, forever.
What? No.
But you can remove it, right?
I can not, I'm sorry Kristoff.
If it was her head that would be easy
but only an act of true love
can thaw a frozen heart.
An act of true love?
A true love's kiss, perhaps?
Anna, we've got to get you back to Hans.
Hans.
Pull us out, Sven.
-- - Olaf! Come on. - I'm coming!
Let's go kiss Hans! Who is this Hans?!
We are here to find Princess Anna.
Be on guard
but no harm is to come to the Queen.
-- - Do you understand? - Yes, Sir.
The Queen.
Go, go!
Get on!
Up there! Come on!
We got her.
No, please.
Stay away!
Fire! Fire!
Get her! Get her!
Queen Elsa!
Don't be the monster they fear you are.
... No. What... what have I done?
Why did you bring me here?
I couldn't just let them kill you.
But I'm a danger to Arendelle.
Get Anna.
Anna has not returned.
If you would just stop the winter
bring back summer. Please.
Don't you see? I can't.
You have to tell them to let me go.
I will do what I can.
Just hang in there. Come on, buddy, faster!
I'll meet you guys at the castle!
Stay out of sight, Olaf!
I will!
It's Princess Anna!
... Are you g... gonna be okay?
Don't worry about me.
Anna! Oh, you had us worried sick...
My Lady.
Get her warm and find Prince Hans, immediately.
We will. Thank you.
Make sure she's safe!
I'm going back out to look for Princess Anna.
You cannot risk going out there again.
... If anything happens to her...
If anything happens to the Princess
you are all Arendelle has left.
He's in here. Prince Hans.
Anna. You're so cold.
-- - Hans, you have to kiss me. - What?
Now.
-- - Now.- Settle down.
We'll give you two some privacy.
What happened out there?
Elsa struck me with her powers.
You said she'd never hurt you.
I was wrong.
Anna?
She froze my heart
and only an act of true love can save me.
A true love's kiss.
Oh, Anna...
If only there was someone out there who loved you.
What?
You said you did.
As thirteenth in line in my own kingdom
I didn't stand a chance.
... I knew...
I'd have to marry into the throne somewhere.
What are you talking about?
As heir, Elsa was preferable, of course.
But no one was getting anywhere with her.
-...- - But you... - Hans?
You were so desperate for love.
You were willing to marry me, just like that.
I figured, after we married
I'd have to stage a little accident for Elsa.
Hans. No, stop.
But then she doomed herself
and you were dumb enough to go after her.
Please.
All that's left now is to kill Elsa
and bring back summer.
You're no match for Elsa.
No, you're no match for Elsa.
I, on the other hand, am the hero
who is going to save Arendelle from destruction.
You won't get away with this.
Oh, I already have.
Please, somebody help.
Please, please!
It's getting colder by the minute.
If we don't do something soon
we'll all freeze to death.
--... - Prince Hans. - Princess Anna is...
-- - dead. - What...?
What happened to her?
She was killed by Queen Elsa.
Her own sister.
At least we got to say our marriage vows
before she died in my arms.
There can be no doubt now.
Queen Elsa is a monster
and we are all in grave danger.
Prince Hans, Arendelle looks to you.
With a heavy heart
I charge Queen Elsa of Arendelle with treason
and sentence her to death.
Hurry up!
She's dangerous. Move quickly and be careful.
-- - The door's not open! - It's frozen.
What is it, buddy? Hey, watch it.
What's wrong with you?
I don't understand you when you talk like that.
Ah! Stop it! Put me down!
No, Sven! We're not going back!
She's with her true love.
... What the...
Anna!
Come on! Come on, boy!
Help.
Anna. Oh no.
Olaf? Olaf. Get away from there.
So this is heat. I love it.
Ooh! But don't touch it!
So, where's Hans? What happened to your kiss?
I was wrong about him. It wasn't true love.
But we ran all the way here?
Please Olaf, you can't stay here
you'll melt.
I am not leaving here
until we find some other act of true love to save you.
Do you happen to have any ideas?
I don't even know what love is.
That's okay, I do.
... Love is...
putting someone else's needs before yours
like, you know
how Kristoff brought you back here to Hans
and left you forever.
Kristoff loves me?
Wow, you really don't know anything about love, do you?
Olaf, you're melting.
Some people are worth melting for.
Just maybe not right this second.
Don't worry, I've got it!
... We're going to get through...
Oh, wait. Hang on. I'm getting something.
It's Kristoff and Sven!
They're coming back this way.
They... they are?
Wow, he's really moving fast.
I guess I was wrong.
I guess Kristoff doesn't love you enough to leave you behind.
Help me up, Olaf. Please.
No, no, no, no, no.
You need to stay by the fire and keep warm.
-- - I need to get to Kristoff. - Why?
Oh, oh, oh, I know why.
There's your act of true love right there
riding across the fjords like a valiant
pungent reindeer King!
Come on!
Look out!
Back this way!
We're trapped.
Slide, Anna.
We made it!
Go, Go, Go, Go...
Come on, buddy, faster.
Kristoff!
Keep going!
... No...
Sven!
Good boy.
Kristoff.
Anna!
Elsa.
You can't run from this!
-- - Just take care of my sister. - Your sister?
She returned from the mountain weak and cold.
She said you froze her heart.
I tried to save her, but it was too late.
Her skin was ice. Her hair turned white.
Your sister is dead... because of you.
No!
Kristoff?
Anna!
Elsa?
No!
Anna!
Oh, Anna... no... no, please no.
Anna.
Anna?
Oh, Elsa.
You sacrificed yourself for me?
I love you.
An act of true love will thaw a frozen heart.
... Love will thaw...
Love. Of course.
- - - Elsa? - Love.
I knew you could do it.
Hands down, this is the best day of my life
and quite possibly the last.
Oh, Olaf. Hang on, little guy.
Hey, my own personal flurry.
Anna? But she froze your heart.
The only frozen heart around here is yours.
Fantastic!
I will return this scoundrel to his country.
We shall see
what his twelve big brothers think of his behavior.
Arendelle thanks you, my Lord.
This is unacceptable.
I am innocent. I'm a victim of fear.
I've been traumatized. Ow! My neck hurts.
Is there a doctor I could see? No.
I demand to see the Queen!
I have a message from the Queen.
Arendelle will henceforth and forever
no longer do business of any sort with Weaseltown.
Weselton. It's Weselton!
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on!
Ow, Okay, Okay, here I come.
-...- - Pole... - Oops. So Sorry.
Okay. Okay. Here we are.
I owe you a sled.
Are you serious?
Yes. And it's the latest model.
No. I can't accept this.
You have to. No returns. No exchanges. Queen's orders.
She's named you the official Arendelle Ice Master and Deliverer.
-- - What? That's not a thing. - Sure it is.
And it even has a cup holder. Do you like it?
Like it? I love it!
I could kiss you!
... I could. I mean I'd like to. I'd...
...... May I? We me...
I mean, may we?
Wait, what?
We may.
Summer!
Hello.
Are you ready?
I like the open gates.
We are never closing them again.
Oh, Elsa, they're beautiful
... but you know I don't ska...
Come on, you can do it!
Look out! The reindeer is coming through!
I don't got it. I don't got it!
Hey, guys!
Olaf!